A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller photographs, Photo Files, RG 1 FA1128
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Civic, 1900 - 2007; 4
  - General, 1938-2002; 1
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1970s, 1987; Black and white 8x10 print; 2 5x7 color prints in a 9.5 x 11.75 double mat. (Box 4, Folder 75)
      LSR and DR at unidentified event at the Cloisters, 1970s; LSR, MFR, DR and unidentified couple in formal dress before portrait painting of woman; front steps of museum with banners for Lila Acheson Wallace Wing and other exhibits. Some photos removed from frame.
    - Mirror Repertory Company, 1984; Color 8 x 11.5 print. (Box 4, Folder 76)
      Photo of Sabra Jones and cast of unidentified production. Photo by Michael Heller, NY, 1984. Photo no. 5211.
    - Mirror Repertory Company, 1984-1985; OVERSIZED 16 x 20" color prints. (Box O 39)
      Photo of full company, inscribed to LSR from Sabra Jones. Cast photos of Sabra Jones as Sadie Thompson and of Geraldine Page. Photos by Michael Heller and by Armen Kachaturian.
    - Moses, Robert (All Long Island Dinner), 1937 April 3; OVERSIZED Panoramic black and white 12 x 20 glossy print. Image stable but damaged from folding. Emulsion cracking in some places. (Box O 138)
      All Long Island Dinner tendered by the Long Island Association to the Hon. Robert Moses, Hotel Pennsylvania. Group photo, LSR and MFR at Table 52. Photograph by Standard Flashlight Co., NY.
    - Museum of Modern Art (Gala), 1998 November 18; Color 8.5x12 print (Box 4, Folder 77)
      Photo of LSR with DR and Happy Rockefeller. Photo copyright NY Times.
    - National Geographic Society, 1957, 1976, 1978, 1984-1987, 1989; OVERSIZED 11x14 black and white photo, 12x15 color photo, glued to mat (Box O 29)
      Group portrait, Trustees Meetings, National Geographic Society, December 1957; September 1976, 1978, 1984-1987; November 1987; and September 1989. (LSR present only in 1957 and 1978 photos.) Photos include identifications.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Public Service Award Dinner, 1994 May 24; OVERSIZED black and white matted print, 4.5 x 6.5 in a 10 x 10.5 mat. (Box O 29)
      Gerald and Betty Ford, with LSR and Mary French Rockefeller, at the award dinner, held at the Waldorf Astoria. Ford was the 1994 recipient of the award conferred by the Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government, SUNY. Photo removed from frame.
    - New York Hall of Science Awards Gala, 1999 November 18; 1 5x7 color print. (Box 4, Folder 78)
      Chelsea Piers, New York City. LSR with Mrs. Evan (Marie "Bootsie") Galbraith. Includes program from event.
    - (New York Public Library), 1980s; 1 black and white glossy print. (Box 4, Folder 79)
      LSR, Happy Rockefeller, Jay Iselin (of public television station Channel 13), and unidentified, in formal attire, standing outside unidentified event. Photo no. 5224. Photographer: Anne Day.
    - New York Republican Victory Dinner, 1959 January 28; Oversized. 12 x 20" black and white glossy print (2 copies). (Box O 138)
      Panoramic photo. Includes NAR and Mary Clark Rockefeller on dais. Also identified: Thomas Dewey, J. Richardson Dilworth. Photo by Empire Photographers, New York. Photo marked on back, D(rawer) 9.
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Pocantico Conference Center, 1994 or later; Color 8x10 print. (Box 4, Folder 80)
      Image of family members and staff at RBF Conference Center. Includes LSR, DR, Abby O'Neill, and others.
    - Round Table, 1988; OVERSIZED Color 11x14 print. (Box O 29)
      Caricature drawing of fortieth anniversary celebration of the Round Table. Photo of a painting by Charlotte Boggs. Includes image of LSR as waiter. The organization has not been identified.
    - San Francisco Convention and Visitors Bureau, Undated; OVERSIZED black and white 9.5 x 12.25 photo attached to 13.75 x 16.5 fabric mat. (Box O 29)
      Unidentified event: LSR christening a "cable car" booth, as officials look on. Photo inscribed: To Laurence, Thanks for launching this car, Jack (Bowen?). Photo removed from frame. Some crinkling damage to lower left corner of photo.
    - Senators' Club Luncheon, 1987 November 20; Color 4x6 prints. (Box 4, Folder 81)
      LSR with Orren Hatch and others. Includes covering letter from Senator Rudy Boschwitz.
    - Travel Program for Foreign Diplomats, Inc., 1977-1978; Black and white 8x10 images. (Box 4, Folder 82)
      Photographs from 1977 conference trip programs. File includes some pamphlets and copies of correspondence. No evidence of LSR involvement, but LSR may have been approached as chair of the RBF.
    - Unidentified event, 1990s; OVERSIZED Black and white, matted and glued to 9.75 x 13 mat board. (Box O 29)
      LSR and MFR with unidentified man, who is introducing young boy to them. Photo was framed in Georgetown, TX. Removed from frame.
    - United Cerebral Palsy, 1950s-1960s; 6 black and white 8x10 glossy prints (Box 4, Folder 83)
      Formal dinner, LSR on dais and with various men and women. Photo numbers 5229-5234.
    - United Nations Association, 1995; 5 black and white 5x7 prints (and duplicates), plus 5 5x7 negatives. One color 5x7 print. (Box 4, Folder 84)
      Thirty-seventh UN Association Ball, April 25, 1995: LSR, DR, MFR, and others (photographer: Mary Hilliard). Dinner, October 24, 1995, in honor of Kim Young Sam, president of the Republic of Korea: LSR, MFR.
    - United Nations Conference on the Human Environment, 1972; Black and white 7x9-8x10 prints. (Box 4, Folder 85)
      LSR as U.S. delegate at the Stockholm Conference. Includes MFR and others.
    - United Service Organization Luncheon, 1986 May 15; 6 black and white 8x10 glossy prints. (Box 4, Folder 86)
      LSR, MFR, Brooke Shields, Robert H. B. Baldwin, at USO Luncheon at the Plaza Hotel. Photographer: D'Arlene Studio. Photos nos. 5662-5664.
    - Welcome Home Dinner for Captain Eddie Rickenbacker, 1943 January 19; OVERSIZED black and white print, 10 x 20. FRAGILE. Photo was folded and the emulsion is cracked along multiple folds. (Box O 138)
      Dinner "given by his friends of Washington, DC," at the Mayflower Hotel. Group photo of banquet, includes LSR. Photo by Schutz Photo.
    - YWCA, 1955-1994 (Box 4, Folder 87)
      MFR at YWCA centennial dinner, 1955; and World Service Day, 1981 (photos nos. 5673-5674). Also in file: Legacy of Leadership program, 1990; clipping on 1994 Charlotte, NC, reception honoring MFR.
    - YWCA ("Aim, Action, Achievement" Film), 1968 April 17; Color 8x10 prints (3). (Box 4, Folder 88)
      Presentation at the White House of YWCA film "Aim, Action, Achievement" (concerning trail building project in Grand Teton National Park). Lady Bird Johnson, LSR, and MFR, and 2 young women.
    - YWCA, 2002 October 18; Color 4x6 snapshots, with negatives. (Box 4, Folder 89)
      YWCA World Service Council Meeting. Includes Ruth Haupert. (No LSR.)
  - Conservation, Parks, and Preservation, circa 1900 - 2007; 2
    - Conservation - General, 1950-1993; 24 black and white and color slides. (Box 4, Folder 90)
      Slides tracing LSR's conservation interests from the New York Zoological Society and Aquarium, ORRRC, Virgin Islands National Park, Congressional Medal, and Marsh Billings Rockefeller National Park. (Slides (produced by Modern Age lab) are presumably reproductions of images found elsewhere in the collection.)
    - Conservation - General, 1966-1988, undated; Color snapshots 3.5 x 4 - 4x6; 2 black and white 8x10 images. (Box 4, Folder 91)
      LSR with various unidentified groups: at unidentified chair lift, 1966; at JY Ranch; with Lady Bird Johnson in Texas (?); on the Hudson River?, 1988. Two images of LSR receiving copy of FDR and Conservation, from Roosevelt Library Director James E. O'Neill, June 11, 1971 (photos nos. 5227-5228).
    - Conservation - General (National Parks Portfolio), Undated; OVERSIZED and VERY HEAVY. Cloth portfolio box, fitted in wooden suitcase, 27 x 23 x 3. Color photos mounted on mat boards with printed inscriptions. (Box O 142)
      Oversized portfolio of mounted photos of national parks with haiku inscriptions. Given to LSR and the Rockefeller Family on behalf of the American People. Cloth portfolio box, fitted in wooden suitcase. Brochure from 1972 dedication of the John D. Rockefeller Jr. Memorial Highway inserted in portfolio.
    - Conservation - General (Views), Undated; OVERSIZED Color prints approximately 6x8 - 8x11, mounted on 11/11.5 x 14 mats. (Box O 30)
      Scenic views of Adirondack lake (photo by Gary Randorf); view from above of a forested lake, location not identified (composite image from 3 photos, removed from frame); unidentified scene of barns and painted fence rails (Vermont?) (removed from frame); Wyoming views (Yellowstone?) (2 images).
    - American Conservation Association: Cluster Development, 1964-1965; OVERSIZED 8x10 - 11x14 black and white prints. (Box O 30)
      Examples of cluster development; many used as illustrations in William H. Whyte, Cluster Development(ACA, 1964).
    - Boscobel, 1968 May; Black and white 8x10 print. (Box 4, Folder 92)
      LSR and MFR with Lila Acheson and Dewitt Wallace and Lady Bird Johnson at Boscobel (May 17, 1968). Photo no. 5433.1. Image sent to LSR by George V. Grune, May 1, 1986.
    - Central Park Conservancy, 1989; 1 Color 8x10 print (Box 4, Folder 93)
      LSR signing oversized check for $35 million, made out to Central Park. Mayor Edward Koch and others in background. Photo enclosed in letter from Elizabeth Barlow Rogers, Central Park Administrator, to LSR, May 8, 1989.
    - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks, 1993 September; Oversized Magnetic album 11.5 x 10.75 x 2 (pages 9x11). (Box O 31)
      Album of captioned photos from reception and dinner given for the Christian Ministry Board by LSR and MFR (at Valley Ranch), and by Caroline and Leonard Firestone. Postcard attached to cover of album from Robert G. and Dorothy J. Koenig to Laurance and Mary.
    - Conservation Service Award (U.S. Department of the Interior), 1962 May 25; Black and white 8x10 and 2x4 prints (Box 4, Folder 94)
      Stewart Udall presenting LSR with Conservation Service Award plaque and group photo, with identifications. Copy of PR photo inscribed: "For Laurance - Who won it many times over! Stewart."
    - Grand Teton Lodge Company, circa 1975 - early 1980s; Black and white 8x10 print; color 8x10 print and 5 copies. (Box 4, Folder 95)
      Vernon Johnson of GTLC and Horace Albright, circa 1975 (photo no. 5706); Board of Directors meeting, early 1980s. Group photo includes LSR; identifications added.
    - Grand Teton Lodge Company, 1964; Black and white 4x5 proof prints (Box 5, Folder 96)
      Public relations photos by Glen Fishback of lodging, conference, and recreation facilities in Grand Teton National Park, 1964. Photos removed from ring-bound album.
    - Grand Teton Lodge Company, 1964-1965; Black and white 4x5 proof prints; 2 contact sheets. (Box 5, Folder 97)
      Public relations photos by Glen Fishback of lodging, conference, and recreation facilities in Grand Teton National Park, 1964. Two contact sheets of GTLC views and of Lady Bird Johnson, Harold Fabian, LSR, and others at JY Ranch, 1965 September. Photos removed from ring-bound album.
    - Grand Teton National Park: General, 1929-1990, undated; Mainly black and white, 8x10 prints; a few negatives and color prints. (Box 5, Folder 98)
      General and historic landscape and views; public relations photos; Transfiguration Chapel. Opening ceremonies, 1929; LSR presenting land deed to Secretary of Interior Oscar L. Chapman, 1949. Includes LSR, Kenneth Chorley, Lady Bird Johnson, Stewart Udall. Includes photos nos. 5203, 5205, 5613, 5702, 5714-5715. Undated and unidentified image of 2 men.
    - Grand Teton National Park: General, circa 1930; FRAMED Black and white photo, approx. 7x12, in 8.5 x 13.5 wooden frame. Some emulsion damage. Photo may be adhered to glass; some water damage prior to framing. Paper backing is beginning to detach from frame. (Box 5, Folder 99)
      Candid group image of Dude Ranchers Association secretary T. Joe Cahill and founder Irving Hastings "Larry" Larom, Secretary of the Interior Ray Lyman Wilbur, and National Park Service director Horace Albright, standing together in field, film camera in background. Framed photo given to LSR and to George Lamb, American Conservation Association, from Oakleigh Thorne, II. Identifications added on back of frame.
    - Grand Teton National Park: General, 1950s; Color slides and 3x5 Pavelle prints. (Box 5, Folder 100)
      Views from Jackson Lake Lodge, picture window views, lodging; Chapel of the Transfiguration; buffalo. Includes image of Kenneth Chorley and others; new barn at JY Ranch.
    - Grand Teton National Park: Chapel of the Transfiguration, 1950s; Color 5x7 Pavelle and Kodak prints; 3x5 color print mounted on card stock. (Box 5, Folder 101)
      Views of Chapel of the Transfiguration (photos removed from paper frames, which were marked Drawer 13: Wyoming). Undated photograph and LSR Christmas card of Chapel of the Transfiguration
    - Grand Teton National Park: Chapel of the Transfiguration, 1963; OVERSIZED Color 10.5 x 13.5 image on 14 x 17 mat. (Box O 130)
      View of Chapel of the Transfiguration. Photo by Oakley Counts, entitled "Worship at Jackson Hole, 1963."
    - Grand Teton National Park: Colter Bay Indian Arts Museum, 1972 July; Black and white 8x10 prints. 1 copy negative. (Box 5, Folder 102)
      LSR, Kenneth Chorley, Harold Fabian, Gary Everhardt, and others at dedication of Colter Bay Indian Arts Museum. File includes correspondence and clipping concerrning photos and ceremonies. Photographer: Elizabeth McCabe.
    - Grand Teton National Park: John D. Rockefeller Jr. Memorial Parkway, 1972; Color mainly 8x10 prints; one black and white 3x5 print (Box 5, Folder 103)
      LSR, MFR, Harold Fabian, Horace Albright, and others at ribbon-cutting and dedication of parkway connecting Yosemite and Grand Teton National Parks. Includes photo no. 5397.
    - Grand Teton National Park: Laurance S. Rockefeller Preserve and Moose Visitor Center, 2007; Color 4x6 snapshots. (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Pre-opening, interior and exterior views of Visitor Center at LSR Preserve and views of Moose Visitor Center. Images taken by Ellen Pomeroy?
    - Grand Teton National Park: Lucas Cabin, 1980s?; 4 black and white 5x7 photos (Box 5, Folder 105)
      Ceremony, with LSR and MFR on dais; group photo; LSR speaking with NPS official. Identification attached to file states "Occasion of Mrs. Fabian donating her cabin, The Lucas Place, to the National Park Service - Jackson, Wy."
    - Grand Teton National Park: Postcards, 1950s-1980s; Black and white and color 3x5-6x8 printed postcards. (Box 5, Folder 106)
      Assorted postcards.
    - Grand Teton National Park: Views, Undated; OVERSIZED colored photo, approximately 8.5 x 16. (Box O 30)
      Hand-colored image of river or lake with Tetons in background and reflected in the water. Photo copyright Stimson, Cheyenne. Removed from frame.
    - Grand Teton National Park: Views, Undated; OVERSIZED color print 12x16 in 16x20 mat. (Box O 130)
      Snake River with Tetons in background. Pencilled note on back: Photo by Mr. Delmar Duvall. Sender: C. R. Carpenter. Stamped on back: Photo by Photographic Services, Central Extension, Pennsylvania State College, Negative no. 3388-6. Photo removed from frame.
    - Greenacre Park, 1971; Black and white 8x10 prints. (Box 5, Folder 107)
      LSR and Abby Rockefeller Mauz‚ at dedication ceremonies for Greenacre Park, East 51st Street, New York. Two images.
    - Historic Hudson Valley: Montgomery Place (General), Undated; Black and white 8x10 prints. (Box 5, Folder 108)
      Two views of stone wall and urns along the river bank. Photo nos. 5111-5112. Photos by Charles Eggert. Montgomery Place attribution supplied in processing.
    - Historic Hudson Valley: Montgomery Place Opening, 1988 June; Color 3x5 prints, and 4x6 prints in small plastic album. (Box 5, Folder 109)
      LSR, Helen Hayes, at ribbon-cutting ceremony, June 11, 1988 (3 snapshots). Album including LSR, MFR, and an unidentified young couple, and general photos of grounds and d‚cor (no photos of the opening specifically). File includes some duplicates.
    - Historic Hudson Valley: Montgomery Place Opening, 1988 June; Color 3.5 x 5 prints. (Box 5, Folder 110)
      Informal photos of LSR with Helen Hayes at opening weekend. Includes MFR, Nash and Bette Castro, Wes Frye. Letter from Bette Castro enclosing photos, June 16, 1988?
    - Historic Hudson Valley: Pocantico Society, 1995 May 16; Color 4x6 photos in small plastic-spiral-bound album (6.75 x 5.25) (Box 6, Folder 111)
      Gathering at the home of LSR and MFR, May 16, 1995. At 834 Fifth Avenue.
    - Historic Hudson Valley: Pocantico Society, 1997 June 16; OVERSIZED color 5x7 photos in large 12.75 x 11 x 1.25 postbound magnetic album. (Box O 32)
      Annual Spring Gathering at the home of LSR, June 16, 1997. At 834 Fifth Avenue. Special guests Kitty Carlisle Hart, Peter Duchin, and cabaret singer Mary Cleere Haran. Includes photos of Lucy Waletzky and (Naomi Waletzky); Ruth Haupert; unidentified. letter of acknowledgement from LSR to Kathy Coulam at HHV, October 8, 1997, inserted inside album cover.
    - Hudson Highlands State Park, 1970 May 23, undated; Black and white and color prints, 3x5-8x10. Includes contact sheet and 3 color negative. (Box 6, Folder 112)
      Dedication ceremony. LSR, NAR. Protest by correction officers in background. Includes photo 5218. Views of Breakneck Mountain and of the park from Storm King. Photos used in Jackson Hole Preserve Inc.: Fiftieth Anniversary, 1940-1990.
    - Hudson Highlands State Park, 1970 May 23; OVERSIZED color 11x14 print. (Box O 30)
      NAR speaking at podium with NYS seal; LSR on platform; possibly with Henry Diamond. (Enlargement of photo 5218).
    - Hudson River Valley Commission, 1966; Black and white 8x10 print and negative. (Box 6, Folder 113)
      New Yorker cartoon (June 18, 1966 issue) concerning LSR's selection to head the commission.
    - Hudson River Valley Commission (Temporary), 1966; OVERSIZED FRAMED black and white print (approx. 11 x 11) in 15.5 x 15 frame. (Box O 40)
      LSR, chair, presenting the Commission's Report to Governor NAR. Back of frame inscribed in pencil in LSR's hand: "To Bill - The master planner, from his devoted friend & admirer." Framed photo.
    - Jackson Hole Preserve Inc., 1956-1993, undated (Box 6, Folder 114)
      JHPI board meetings (group photos and candids, including meeting at JY Ranch), staff (unidentified), projects. Jackson Hole airport; Jackson Lake Lodge. Joint meeting with American Conservation Association, 1993. Includes LSR, MFR, Lady Bird Johnson, Kenneth Chorley, Conrad Wirth, William H. Whyte, George Lamb, Nash Castro. Photos nos. 5060, 5397, 5693-5716, with gaps.
    - Jackson Hole Preserve Inc., 1961; Color slides (19) on slide card. One color 5x7 print; one 8x10 black and white print. (Box 6, Folder 115)
      Images of LSR, Chorley, Fabian, Albright (and others) at Lunch Tree Hill and Jackson Lake, campfire, and rafting. Includes MFR. Possible board meeting? Prints of Chorley and LSR (profile view) and of Fabian, Albright, and Chorley at Lunch Tree Hill
    - Jackson Hole Preserve Inc., 1960s; OVERSIZED color 12.5 x 16.5 print mounted on 18.5 x 23 linen mat. (Box O 130)
      Group photo of JHPI board at Grand Teton National Park. Includes identifications. Removed from frame.
    - Jackson Hole Preserve Inc., 1967 September; OVERSIZED color 9 x 13.75 print glued to 18.25 x 14.5 mat and board. (Box O 130)
      Board meeting, JY Ranch, September 1967. Photo by Anne Revis Grosvenor, copyright National Geographic Society, 1967. Three copies; one removed from frame. One copy badly faded.
    - Jackson Hole Preserve Inc., 1993 October 16-17; Album (approx. 4.5 x 6.5 x 2) of color 4x6 prints. (Box 6, Folder 116)
      Joint Board meeting of JHPI and the American Conservation Association, Woodstock, VT.
    - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park, 1948 July; Black and white 5x7 and 8x10 prints. (Box 6, Folder 117)
      LSR speaking at dedication of wildlife park. Two photos, with identifications. Includes Fairfield Osborn.
    - Jackson Lake Lodge: General, 1953-1955; Black and white 8x10 glossy prints (Box 6, Folder 118)
      LSR, Kenneth Chorley, and others, reviewing furnishings for Jackson Lake Lodge; architectural drawings of lodge development; construction photo
    - Jackson Lake Lodge: General, Undated; 3 color 8x10-8.5x11 prints; 2 color negatives. (Box 6, Folder 119)
      Aerial views of lodge development; entrance sign
    - Jackson Lake Lodge: Opening, 1955 June; Black and white, mainly 8x10 prints; one 9.5 x 12.5 print. (Box 6, Folder 120)
      Candid photos from various sources of LSR, Kenneth Chorley, Harold Fabian, and others at reception or dinner for opening of Jackson Lake Lodge. Image of LSR and Chorley at Open House, June 12, 1955. (No photos of opening ceremonies per se.)
    - Kipahulu Addition (Haleakala National Park), 1969 January 10; Black and white 8x10 prints, multiple copies. (Box 7, Folder 121)
      LSR, Stewart Udall, and others, at signing ceremony for addition of Kipahulu to Haleakala National Park, Maui.
    - Montana, 1920s; Black and white 6.5 x 9.75 - 7x11 prints. (Box 7, Folder 122)
      Undated commerically printed scenic photos of Glacier National Park; photo of Rockefeller party campsite, with LSR note on back: "Early morning breakfast on camping trip in Montana."
    - Mount Hood, Undated; Black and white (sepia) 4x10 matte prints. (Box 7, Folder 123)
      Set of 6 commercially printed scenic photos of Mount Hood. Stamped on back: The Mount Hood Loop Highway.
    - Mount Rainier National Park, 1950s-1960s; Color 5x7 prints in 8x9 signed and labeled portfolio mats. (Box 7, Folder 124)
      Four scenic photos labeled and signed by Melville B. Grosvenor. Photos taken from a hotel site proposed by the NPS overlooking the Nisqually River.
    - National Association of Audubon Societies Convention, 1935 October 28; Oversized Panoramic sepia tone 12 x 20 glossy print. Image stable but damaged from folding. (Box O 138)
      Thirty-First Annual Convention, American Museum of Natural History. LSR and MFR seated at table (2nd row from right of photo, 3rd table from the center front). Photograph by Standard Flashlight Co., NY.
    - National Park Foundation, 1971-1977, undated; Black and white and color 5x7 - 8x10 prints. (Box 7, Folder 125)
      Group photos of LSR with the National Park Foundation board and with Secretary of the Interior Rogers Morton.
    - National Park Service, 1975; Color 5x7 prints in 8x10 mats. (Box 7, Folder 126)
      Photo of Grand Teton National Park, inscribed to LSR from Gary Everhardt, director of the NPS, September 8, 1975: Dear Laurance / I wish to thank you for your support of the goals & objectives of the National Park Service." Photo of LSR with Everhardt.
    - National Recreation and Park Association, 1967 December; OVERSIZED black and white 8x10 print glued to 11x17 mat board (Box O 30)
      Congress, December 1967. Photo of LSR and Florida governor Claude Kirk. Inscribed "Your leadership and meeting were both great and ultimate success for Florida unquestionable. Best regards, Claude Kirk"
    - New York State (General), 1964, 1967; Black and white and color 8x10 prints. (Box 7, Folder 127)
      Ice jams at Niagara Falls, January 27, 1964 (Photos nos. 5151-5153); unidentified wintry landscape views (Hudson River valley and lake?), prints dated 1967 (Photos nos. 5145-5150).
    - New York State? (Unidentified), 1989 Fall; Color 3.5 x 5 prints. (Box 7, Folder 128)
      Lady Bird Johnson, Bette Castro, Larry Rockefeller and others at unidentified gathering (rustic lodge, lake, black bear).